ctrader.com 2016-12-07

# Privacy Policy

Our Privacy Policy applies to information and data collected on our website or through our products by Spotware Systems Ltd. and its affiliated partners.

Spotware.com **does not automatically collect any personal information** from visitors to the website, and we do not request by default any identifiable information.

In certain cases, such as for the opening of demo or live accounts for our various products, Spotware Systems Ltd or our partners may require specific information from you, such as your name and email address – and may use this information to help verify your identity, for any necessary correspondence, or to help us meet the specific needs of our visitors.

If a live account is opened with any Spotware affiliated broker, **Spotware does not control information passed through their website or through any communication with them**. Please refer to the broker’s privacy policy for details.

**Control of your information**

If you would specifically not like particular information to be used as a basis for contact with you, please notify us at info@spotware.com. We will make every effort to respond in a timely manner to requests to correct inaccuracies in personal or identifiable information.

**Information protection**

Any personal information submitted through the website contact forms or through any of the platforms is protected by technical and organizational measures such as data encryption to help keep your information secure and current.

**Cookies**

Spotware.com uses internet cookies to facilitate easier navigation throughout the website and increase visitor convenience. Your internet browser is likely to accept these cookies by default, however you can refer to your browser’s help guide if you would like to reject or delete them from your system.

We may use both "session" cookies and "persistent" cookies on the website. We will use the session cookies to: keep track of you whilst you navigate the website; and other uses. We will use the persistent cookies to: enable our website to recognise you when you visit; and other uses.

Session cookies will be deleted from your computer when you close your browser. Persistent cookies will remain stored on your computer until deleted, or until they reach a specified expiry date.

Cookies used by spotware.com do not retrieve any personal information or any information from the visitor’s computer.

**Third Parties**

Spotware does not share, sell, or otherwise transmit any information, personal or otherwise, collected through the website, platforms, or through correspondence, with any third parties or affiliated companies. Any information is kept securely and is confidential.

**Changes to this Privacy Statement**

Spotware will post any changes made to the privacy statement on this page and through other communication mediums we deem appropriate for our users to be aware of any changes that are made which information is collected and how it is used.
